#### Contact

moyosoluwa.faleye@memorialhermann.org

www.linkedin.com/in/moyo-faleye-a24a5b11 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing Acute Care Inpatient

# Moyo Faleye

MSN, RN, CRRN

**Greater Houston** 

## Summary

Experienced CERTIFIED MSN prepared nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital, ambulatory clinic & health care industry. Skilled in Ambutatory Care Services, Hematology/ Oncology, Stroke Rehabilitation, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Traumatic Brain Injury and Nursing Administration.

# Experience

Memorial Hermann Hospital TMC

Clinic Nurse for Hematology, Malignant Hematology and Palliative Care Oncology Clinic

October 2013 - Present (6 years 11 months)

Houston, Texas

I work with a team of five physicians (5 Hematologists/Oncologist and 2 Palliative Care Physicians) as the Clinic nurse overseeing all patients affairs.

TIRR Memorial Hermann Hospital RN at TIRR Memorial Hermann September 2006 - October 2013 (7 years 2 months)

Loyola University MSN 2011 - 2012 (1 year)

Park Plaza Hospital, Houston Texas Staff Nurse 2005 - 2006 (1 year)

Memorial Hermann Healthcare System Clinical Manager 1999 - 2005 (6 years) Memorial Hermann Continuing Care Hospital

Memorial Hermann Southwest Hospital

Page 1 of 2

Staff Nurse 1998 - 1999 (1 year)

Houston

Initial role as a staff nurse on the Rehab unit, and was later transferred to the Skilled Nursing Floor as a Charge Nurse.

CHRISTUS Health - St. Joseph Hospital Staff Nurse June 1997 - January 1998 (8 months)

Received my post baccalaureate nursing internship at St. Joseph Hospital and stayed on as Staff nurse on the Skilled Nursing Floor.

### Education

Loyola University New Orleans MSN, Nursing

Texas Woman's University BSN, Nursing